Is the right move here to choke
up on the bat and go swish?
Or else should I go swoosh instead?
No, it's a slider.
It's going to break here and...
Thank you so much for joining us.
Hey, I'm made of way All right.
Monami, our dear comrade?
I can only imagine the
regret from never realizing.
your dream of setting
off the Akiba Big Bang.
But the stardust memory you leave behind
lives on in our hearts for all eternity.
What the hell is she talking about?
And why is Manami's funeral
in this shitty place?
With all the mess with the merger,
Creatureland probably didn't have time.
to make nice arrangements.
How is this a merger?
You gotta be kidding me.
We work for Creatureland now
and the made alien name is gone.
It was a freaking takeover.
So you have a problem with her decision?
Stop your bickering.
We're at a funeral.
Now that the Creatures and
E .T.'s have joined hands,
Miss Minami must be smiling
down on us from the start above.
Well, if it isn't the
fellow from Creatureland.
And who is this with you?
The manager of the Oinky Doink Cafe. Now.
The Oinky Doink Cafe!
Please accept my deepest
condolences for your tragic loss.
We appreciate you coming all
this way for us on this day.
Such a sad and unexpected tragedy.
These must be such
difficult times for you.
You're the one to talk.
Having lived your lives as alien
invaders and adventurers of space.
You may find some of our ways odd.
If there is anything we as more
experienced creatures can do to?
Ms.
Ugaki and her new friends have
already made a fabulous start as
creatures Their profits have already
exceeded that of Oinky Doink?
With the axolotl as their theme They have
rebranded as the Memory
Lane Animal Cafe axolotls.
You think axolotls are creatures?
Of course they're creatures
What's all this commotion?
Welcome, boss.
Settle the score with this. What?
A friendly game of baseball?
This is an order from our leader.
They've ordered us to play
baseball? Count me out.
I can't be bothered.
For real?
After we tried to murder each other?
That's too funny. Let's do it!
We'll wash away our
differences with our sweat.
We couldn't ask for a more peaceful
solution to all this fighting,
good playing a game with
bats and peacefully.
We'll make sure it does.
We'll happily chase after the
ball together and patch things up.
Whatever we just have
to play along for show.
No,
if we're going to do this we have to
play to win Someone's all fired up,
but can you play baseball
with just seven people?
For all those who fell in the
recent ruckus, a moment of silence.
Nerula, you just watch.
I promise we'll make up and all
become friends during this game.
He said a moment of silence, jackass.
I mean, do we really have
to play ball and all?
We all know who won. Oh, yeah?
What do you mean by that, huh?
Well, like, you quit being aliens and now
you're just asshole toodles or whatever.
That's axolotls!
Get cocky, bottom feeder!
What stop that bottom
feeders like them have
their own struggles to
deal with bottom feeders?
You see I've been impressed
by how unfazed you seem to
be despite being ridiculed
as a burden to creature land!
Hey, now, let's all just have some fun.
This match is partly to commemorate
you becoming axi morons Oh,
or was it asshole toodles?
All right, everyone.
We can settle our disagreements
with baseball Come on.
Let's have fun and play each
other fair and square Damn you.
We'll take you fucking pigs out.
Just you wait.
Forced to change our
persona by creature land?
Our honor as extraterrestrials trampled?
I know all too well
how frustrated you are.
This is war, dammit!
Go show them how we're
eons out of their league!
This is war, pigs! No, it's not!
Who are they calling a damn burden?
I don't care what dirty tricks you use.
Go crush them!
No, we can't!
Playing rough is out of the question!
Come on, now, chief.
We have to win by playing fair and square.
We can't resort to violence now.
We don't want Nerula and the
other's sacrifices to be in vain.
There's no point in all of
this if we don't play fair.
Now let's do this.
Second!
Short stop!
Yumechi! Shippon!
I can't hear you out there!
She's like more of a pain than usual.
First!
Third!
Now to the pitcher!
Come on, outfield!
Let's hear some noise!
Hell! Hell! Si, Hell! Hell!
Who are they?
Some guys chief recruited?
They're supposed to be
really good at baseball.
Zoya says she can't understand
a word they're saying.
Let's play ball!
What are you looking at, pig?
She's fired up.
Yeah, she is.
She looked up to Ms.
Manami.
I'll crush this pitch up to
where you are, Ms. Manami.
You're out.
That pitch came in nice and fast.
Great work, Zoya.
God damn it.
Get your butts out there
and go shut them out!
Hey, batter batter!
Their pitcher hasn't even warmed up yet!
That first pitch will be nice and easy!
Better be ready, Sheepod!
This is such a drag.
Oh crap, I didn't mean to hit that!
Nice batting!
Pitcher's off to a bad start!
Now is our chance!
Ow!
What are you doing, you stupid idiot?
Hey, you!
That's good for us!
What?
Go, Yumechi!
Why the hell am I on base
anyways? Lead off! Lead off!
Runner's gonna run!
I so don't really wanna run.
you act like you've played
before yeah i played
a bit back in the joint
strike strike Batter!
Gotta swing to hit the ball!
You hear that, batter?
I shall swing, then.
Whoa!
Throw it home!
Hey, hey!
You're wasting our time, Asphibians! Ugh!
What the hell are you all doing?
You know, I actually
used to play softball.
Strike! Huh?
All right, I got this.
There! Yeah!
That's strike three!
Batter's out!
Yep, I've got the timing down now.
Never mind, never mind!
Shake it off, Team Pig!
All right, crush those amphibians!
Come on, secret weapon!
Strike them out if you wanna live!
Ball!
Strike!
You're out!
Didn't you say they were good at baseball?
What are they doing?
What's the deal with those guys?
They're foreign exchange students.
I'm at an electric town buying cameras.
It's time we end fair play.
Go crush those pigs.
Okay, coach, we got this.
All right, I think it's time we
start this game for real now.
That's strike two.
She won't hit it! Batter's blind!
Batter's blind!
Oh, just watch me.
Hey, Nogome!
Nagomi!
Are you all right?
Chief, call an ambulance.
Are you sure we need an ambulance?
What's the big fuss?
I barely even hit her.
Oops, sorry, my bad.
Why, you little bitch!
Well, you're the one who started it.
Say that again!
Wait, you're asking!
No, wait, please!
It's my fault, no violence!
Um, I, I interfered.
I leaned in way too close!
What?
Catcher's interference.
Batter goes to first.
Seriously?
Honestly, that assy
moron's the one to blame.
I think you should go sit
down and get some rest.
I want to see this through to the end.
Okay, let's keep our chins up!
Yumechi!
All I did was tag her, she's out.
That was more than that, you bitch!
Cross them!
Cross them all!
What's wrong with all of you?
Why do you always have
to resort to violence?
I just got her out using
my knuckleball. Huh?
What are you even saying?
You're not playing baseball at all!
You're the only one
playing baseball, Nagomi.
Then what are the rest of you doing?
Being a nail-oink!
Oh!
Safe!
What the hell, bitch?
This won't change the way we play.
We have to win, playing fair and square.
Good, we've turned the tables.
Don't let them score any more runs.
Hey, you, take out a mate
or two while you're at it.
Sure thing.
They are totally coming for us, dude.
Let's do this.
I'm ready to rumble.
Is the right move here to choke
up on the bat and go swish?
Or else should I go swoosh instead?
No. It's a slider.
It's going to break here and...
Not again!
Those tricks!
Don't worry, guys. I'm fine.
I'll lead off and put
the pressure on them.
Good luck at the plate!
At this rate, she's gonna
end up dead real quick.
That kid.
You're out!
The three outs, switch!
Let's finish this.
Go out there and crush
every last one of them.
All right.
Hey, you two there, are you listening?
There's a maid out there
who's playing fair and square.
Huh?
There's a maid out there
playing fair and square.
What is this shit?
Are you two arguing with me?
She's out there playing fair and square!
You're gonna do not say fair and square!
Hey, you!
What the hell?
You're out.
Out!
Why, you little...
Yeah, you get back here! For real?
Ronko's playing fair now, too.
But a maid shouldn't have to put
up with someone giving him crap.
You know provoking the
enemy is a futile exercise.
Futile?
Axo, Axo, Axo!
Want me to keep sniffing off your
limbs till they stop growing back?
Shut up, you button-feeted hog!
That's futile, all right.
Out, bitch!
Out!
That's awesome!
Nice play, you two!
I just really want to
get this over with, okay?
Let's finish these lizards off.
You knuckleheads!
Aren't you ashamed this game is so close?
Time out!
When did this happen?
Your nails totally split.
I can still pitch if I rip it off.
Um, I don't think so.
Well, then who's gonna pitch for us now?
Allow me to pitch.
Give me the ball.
But Ronko! You can't!
You're still injured! I'm fine.
All right, Ronko.
Ronko, I'm counting on you.
Come on, everyone!
Let's win this!
Oinkie doink!
Oink! Oink!
Oink, oink, oink!
Now we're on fire!
Even the piggies are their fangs!
Oink!
Listen up, Kasumi!
You do whatever you've
got to do to get on base!
Hey, are you even listening?
Excuse me, I think she's talking to you.
There's no way we're falling
for your stupid tricks.
Stop in there!
We can't lose.
Strike one!
Strike three, you're out! Damn it!
At this frickin' rate,
if we lose to these smelly bottom
feeders, our reputation is done for.
Umpire, I'm pitch hitting!
Is she even allowed to bat?
You know, I can't let things in like this.
After all, I'm the head of
the made alien group, damn it.
No bottom-feeding swine
is going to ever...
Strike one!
Fuck me to turn you into a peroski!
Are you fucking kidding me?
You asshole-lots never learn, do ya?
Everybody stop!
No one's gonna be hitting anyone!
You little f...
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
I did it!
I really did it, Miss Monami!
Miyabi?
Oh, I...
You...
Ronko, we need to call an ambulance now!
how how could this happen i
just wanted to play a proper
game of baseball with no violence or
bloodshed considering
we've had some actual casualties
they're not dead huh hey
what are you that's right
they're not dead right girls yeah
They're not dead!
Let's get back to the dugout, Miss Ugaki.
Come on, let's go, axolotl mascot. What?
They're not dead?
Well, of course, that's
what they said, right?
Oh, yay!
Then we can keep playing baseball!
All right!
Let's turn this bitch up a notch!
Then we'll restart the game.
Let's play ball!
We're going to win!
Yeah!
Hey, check it out.
Their coach looks super intense, huh?
Can't they adjust her angle a little bit?
You're out!
OK, let's finish this game off right!
There's two outs, now let's go!
Dead ball!
Hey, that's cheating!
Shut up, pig!
It's up to you now, El!
I know a lot has happened out
here, but we've made it this far?
and they're playing properly now.
I'm sure we're about to achieve
something amazing on this field today.
We've got to win this!
Okie dokie, oikie doink!
Some nice pitches.
Come on, Elle.
Come on, show them what we're made of!
Let's go, axolotls, let's go!
Let's go, Axolotos! Let's go!
Let's go, Axolotos!
Let's go!
Let's go! Sorry, kid.
I can't let you win.
We can't afford to lose this game, either.
Because beyond this game, I'm sure a
new future is waiting for us maids.
Time to end this.
It's out!
Game's over!
It's done.
We did it!
Damn it.
Those pig heads really beat us.
Yeah, they did. We lost.
But hey, it was a really good game.
Pigs, and we hail thee.
The object of our crime.
Where our bones will be for all time?
Back, back, to sea, and brine!
For our masters tis a theme.
We will serve with smiles.
We snort as pigs.
Nerula, we did it.
We got through a good, honest game.
You've aged, Ronko.
Usuko, you're alive and well.
You assumed I was dead? Yes.
I searched for you,
but it was all in vain.
Ronko, I want you to know I've
climbed to the very top of Akiba.
I now go by the name Nagi.
Nagi?
So does that mean you're the
head of the Creatureland group?
Yes.
What do you suppose Miss Michio
would say if she saw me now?
I must apologize.
It was because of me that Miss Michio...
If only you had taken up your
gun before all that happened.
The made alien woman with the red bat.
You didn't kill her.
That's correct.
That brand of foolishness
got Miss Michio killed.
Is drawing with ketchup the
only thing this hand can do?
I know it's not.
Bronco!
We're about to start our meeting!
All right.
Fight for the sake of the group.
Otherwise, you'll have no place
to call home here in Akiba.
You're a bit too old now for all
this super-duper smooch crap.
Do you know her? I do.
We were once colleagues.
That's quite a super-deluxe
maid outfit she's wearing.
Ugaki was already dead at the end.
I see, then.
What could work by an unexpected intruder?
I believe that should clear
up the last of the obstacles.
Yeah, we'll see.
Congratulations on resuming operations!
I didn't expect the cafe to be back.
Apparently, those three
helped fix up the place.
I wanted Nerula to know
that I was doing fine!
I'm going to Dream Pig and go, go!
DREAM PIG GO! GO!
Fight for the sake of the group.
Otherwise, you'll have no place
to call home here in Akiba.
We'll
be
right back.